So Weiss, you know uh..
Weiss，跟你说..
I was thinking, after this, maybe we could go grab a bite to eat?
我在想这节课后，我们可以去吃点东西
And..
而且..
You know I've got two tickets to that new Spruce Willis movie, if you wanna make the trip to Vale
我还弄了两张Spruce Willis的新电影票，只要你愿意去溪谷市
I hear it's awesome
听说很赞
And then maybe after that we could study together?
之后或许我们还可以一起学习？
I mean, you're smart and I'm a..you know
因为你很聪明，而我..你懂的
And then I..
然后我就..
Oh, uh, timed that one wrong, I guess..
噢，这下课的时机真糟..
Well, the stunning conclusion to this story will have to wait..
那么，这个故事的精彩结局就只能等到..
Until next time
下一节课了
Weiss
Weiss
Did you hear me?
你听到我的话了？
No, no, no, yes
不吃，不看，不学，当然聪明
One day
有朝一日
I thought that class would never end
我以为那门课永远完不了
Alright guys, today is the day
好了民那，就是今天了
The investigation begins!
调查开始！
I'm glad to see we're taking this so seriously
真高兴我们居然如此认真
Hey, we've got a plan
喂，我们是有计划的
That's..moderately serious
这算一般般认真了
Right, everyone remember their roles?
没错，每个人都记得自己的任务吧？
You and I will head to the CCT to check the Schnee records for any other Dust robberies or inconsistencies
你和我去CCT检查雪倪公司其他尘晶抢劫案的记录或不一致的地方
Seeing as I'm in the family, it shouldn't be a problem
既然我是家族成员，应该没有问题
The White Fang has regular faction meetings to hand out orders and recruit new members
白牙会有定期的内部会议来传达命令及招募新人
If I can get in, I can hopefully find out what they're planning
如果我能混进去，基本上就能弄清他们打的算盘
I have an old friend on the shady side of town that typically knows everything going on in Vale
我有个老朋友住在城镇阴面，溪谷发生的事情他都知道
Getting information out of him shouldn't be too hard
从他那儿弄些消息应该不难
Great! We'll meet up tonight near Yang to go over what we found
很好！今晚在Yang那里集合交换情报
Let's do this!
开干吧！
Yeah!
耶！
Sun?!
Sun！？
How did you get up there?
你怎么上来的？
That's easy, I do it all the time
这有何难，我天天这样
You do what?!
你天天干啥！？
I climb trees all the time!
我天天爬树！
So, are we finally getting back at that Torchwick guy?
所以我们终于可以回击那个Torchwick了？
We, are going to investigate the situation..
我们正要去调查目前的情况..
As a team
作为一个小队
Sorry, Sun. We don't wanna get friends involved if we don't have to
抱歉Sun，如果没必要我们不想把朋友坑进来
That's dumb! You should always get friends involved
太傻了，你应该时刻拉朋友入坑
That's why I brought Neptune
所以我带Neptune来了
Sup?
还好嘛？
How did you even get up here?
你这又是怎么上来的？
I have my ways
我自有办法
Seriously though, can I come in?
说真的，我能进去么？
We're like, really high up right now
现在觉得还真的有点高
Alright, I'll go with Weiss
很好，我跟Weiss一起
Sun, you can go with Blake
Sun，你可以和Blake一起
And Neptune, you can go with Yang since she doesn't have a partner
然后Neptune，你可以和Yang一起，她没有搭档
Everyone good?
都没问题吧？
Actually Ruby, why don't you go with Yang?
其实Ruby啊，你为啥不和Yang一起？
After all, she is your sister
毕竟她是你姐姐
But.. Weiss, who would go with you then?
但是Weiss，那样的话谁跟你一起？
Well.. I guess Neptune could come with me
嘛~我觉得Neptune可以跟我一起
Nah~
别逗~
But.. But!
可是..可是！
WOW, I forget how big the transmit tower looks up close!
哇噢，我都忘了近看通讯塔居然这么大！
You should see the one in Atlas
你应该看看阿特拉斯的那个
That was the first one, right?
那是第一个塔吧？
Correct, Atlas developed the cross-continental transmit system to allow the four kingdoms to communicate with one another
没错，阿特拉斯开发了跨洲通讯系统，让四个王国能够互相通信
It was their gift to the world after the Great War
这是战后阿特拉斯送给世界的礼物
Ooh, look at me
哼，快看我
My name is Weiss, I know facts, I'm rich
我叫Weiss，我是学霸，我是壕
Don't be a pest
能不黑么
Besides, the only reason we're here is because you like the tower so much
何况我们在这不都是因为你喜欢看塔？
We could've just as easily made a call from the library
我们本来可以轻松地在图书馆打电话
I know, but it's so cool!
我知道，但这太棒了！
Oh, I'm gonna take a picture..
哦，我得拍个照..
Oh..
噢..
You dropped this
你掉了这个
Penny?!
Penny！？
Uh..
呃..
Where have you been?!
你到哪儿去了！？
We haven't seen you since the night at the docks!
港口那晚以来就没见过你了
Sorry, I think you're confused
抱歉，我觉得你弄错了
Uh.. I've got to go
呃，我要走了
What was that about?
这都啥情况？
I don't know
不知道
But I'm going to find out
不过我会去弄清楚
You go make your call, I'll meet up with you later
你去打电话，我之后会来找你
Wait!
等等
Penny, where have you been?
Penny，你到底去哪儿了？
It's been weeks
这都几周了
There seems to be a.. misunderstanding
你貌似误会了什么
What?!
哈！？
Penny
Penny
Is everything okay?
真的还好么？
Penny, please, stop!
Penny，拜托，停下！
Look
听着
I don't know what's wrong
我虽然不清楚
But you have to listen to me
但你必须听我说
Those guys we fought at the docks
我们在港口打的那些家伙
We think they're up to something big, something bad
我们觉得他们有更大更险恶的阴谋
I need you to tell you what happened to you that night
你得告诉我那天晚上你怎么了
Please. As a friend..
拜托，作为朋友..
It isn't safe to talk here
这里说话不安全
Hello, welcome to the CCT. How may I help you?
你好，欢迎来到CCT，您需要什么帮助？
I'd like to go to the communications room, please?
请带我去通信室，好吗？
Absolutely, could you please place your scroll on the terminal to verify your identity?
当然可以，请把卷轴板放在终端上来确认您的身份
Perfect! Thank you, Miss Schnee
很好！谢谢配合，Schnee小姐
Welcome to the Beacon Cross-Continental Transmit Center. How may I help you?
欢迎来到信标跨洲通讯中心。需要什么帮助？
I need to make a call to Schnee Company World Headquarters in Atlas
我需要跟阿特拉斯的雪倪公司世界总部通话
Absolutely
没有问题
If you could head over to terminal three, I'll patch you through
请您去三号终端，我帮您接通
Thank you
多谢
Hi, mom! How are things back in signal?
嗨，老妈！信号学院那边怎么样了？
Thank you for calling the Atlas..Oh!
感谢您联系阿特拉斯..噢
Miss Schnee! Good afternoon
Schnee小姐！下午好
Would you like me to patch you through to your father? I think your sister Winter might be here as well
想让我帮您转到您父亲那儿吗？您的姐姐Winter应该也在
No thank you
不用了，谢谢
I was actually wondering if you could find some files for me
我其实是想问你能帮我找些文件么
I've compiled a short list
我列了个小清单
I see
原来如此
If you don't mind.. what, may I ask, is this for?
若不介意我问问，这些文件要做什么？
School project
学校的项目
Umm.. There are some sensitive documents on this list, ma'am
呃..清单里有一些敏感文件，小姐
Well then, I'll be sure to treat them with care
那么我保证会小心保管
Right, very well
好吧，没问题
The data's being transferred to your scroll now
数据已经传到您的卷轴板上了
Wonderful, that will be all then
太好了，这样就行了
Are you sure you wouldn't like me to patch you through to your father before you go?
您确定走之前不需要我帮您转接给您父亲？
Yes, I'm sure
是的，不用了啦
Well then, have a nice day
好的，祝您顺利
I wish I could help you, Ruby
我希望我能帮你，Ruby
But I don't know anything about those men
但我一点儿也不了解那伙人
Well, what happened to you that night?
那么，那天晚上你怎么了？
We're all together, and then you just disappeared! Were you kidnapped?
我们都在一起，你就直接消失了！你被绑架了？
Oh No, nothing like that
噢不，没那回事
Well then, where did you go?
那你到底去哪里了？
I've never been to another kingdom before
我以前从没去过其它王国
My father asked me not to venture out too far, but..
我父亲要我在外面别跑太远，不过..
You have to understand, my father loves me very much
你要明白，我父亲非常爱我
He just worries a lot
他只是操心太多
Believe me, I know the feeling
相信我，我懂这感觉
But.. why not let us know you're okay?
但是..你怎么不告诉我们你没事？
I..
我..
was asked..
被要求..
not to talk to you..
不能跟你交谈
or Weiss, or Blake, or Yang
还有Weiss、Blake、Yang
Anybody, really
谁都不行
Was your dad that upset?
你爸爸那样生气？
No
不
It wasn't my father
不是我父亲
The AK-130 has been a standard security norm of Remnant for several years
AK-130作为树不子的正常保安标准已经多年了
And they have done a fine job, wouldn't you agree, wouldn't you agree?
而且它们干得不错，对不对，对不对？
But
但是
The kingdom of Atlas is a kingdom of innovation
阿特拉斯是一个创新的王国
and fine..
而“不错”..
well that's just not good enough, is it?
并不足够好，对吧？
Presenting, the Atlesian Knight
我给你们介绍，阿特拉斯骑士
200!
200！
Smarter, sleeker
更聪明，更圆滑
And admittedly, a little less scary
而且毫无疑问，没那么吓人
These models will come activate later this year, but they won't be alone
这些型号会在下半年启用，而且不止它们
Now, the Atlesian Military though support the idea of removing men from the dangerous of the battlefield
尽管阿特拉斯军方支持把人类从危险战场上替换下来
However, there are still many situations that undoubtedly require..
但还有很多情况明显需要人类..
a human touch
亲自动手
Ruby..
Ruby..
So, our kingdom's greatest minds in cooperation with the Schnee Dust Company
所以，我们王国最顶尖的精英们与雪倪尘晶公司合作研发
are proud to introduce..
荣幸地为您介绍..
The Atlesian Paladin!
阿特拉斯游侠！
Now we couldn't have him here for you today
虽然今天他不能来现场
But these mechanized battle suits will be seen defending the borders of our kingdom within the year!
但这些机械战斗装甲在今年内就能用来保家卫国了！
Ruby
Ruby
Maybe we should go somewhere else
我们应该离开这里
Penny?!
Penny？
Wait?! Where are you going?
等等，你要去哪？
Down here! She went this way
过来，她从这边跑了
This way!
这边！
Penny?
Penny？
Are you okay?!
你没事吧！？
Uh-huh (▔_▔")~
嗯哼~ (▔_▔")
Did you see that?
你看见了？
Oh my god!
我的天！
Do you think she's okay?
你觉得她没受伤？
Penny, come back!
Penny，回来啊！
..call the police?
..不叫警察么？
Did she stop that with bare hands?
她空手就把车停住了？
Penny! Please!
Penny，拜托！
What is going on?!
到底怎么回事！？
Why are you running?!
你为啥要跑！？
How did you do that?!!!
你是怎么做到的！？
I.. I can't
我..不能说
Everything's fine..
没有任何问题
I.. I don't want to talk about it
我..我不想说这些
Penny! If you could just tell me what's wrong, I can help you!
Penny，你只要告诉我到底怎么回事，我能帮你！
No, no no, you wouldn't understand
不，不不，你理解不了
Let me try, you can trust me~
让我试着理解，你要相信我~
You're my friend, right?
你是我朋友，对吧？
You promise you're my friend?
你保证当我的朋友？
I promise
我保证
Ruby..
Ruby..
I'm not a real girl
我不是人类女孩
Oh 0 0..
噢 0 0..
BRB
BRB
This SUB is presented by Baidu RWBY Bar Creator: sbz_kid
本字幕由百度RWBY吧提供 片源/翻译/时间轴/特效/后期：sbz_kid